Oscobo is all about Privacy
===========================

Oscobo respects and protects the privacy of consumers; and is committed to delivering a safe search environment. When you use Oscobo, you trust us with your searches and we understand and value this trust. We have provided this Privacy Policy to explain how Oscobo protects your privacy while searching, what information we collect through Oscobo and some of your privacy rights regarding that information.

Search results are provided by Becovi Ltd.  
_Becovi Ltd_ _5TH Floor, Nova Atria North, Blackthorn Road, Sandyford Business Park, Sandyford, Dublin D18F5X2, Ireland_

Effective March 22, 2023

This Policy may change from time to time. Please check back frequently for updates.

1\. Oscobo does not associate your searches from your online accounts.
----------------------------------------------------------------------

The most popular search engines offer other services which often collect sensitive personal information such as email (Gmail, Outlook Webmail) and social web services (Google+ and YouTube). When you search the web and remain logged into these accounts, your search queries can be easily connected to your profile.

Oscobo completely disconnects your searches from being tied to your email accounts and social profiles.

2\. Request, log or share your personal information.
----------------------------------------------------

Oscobo doesn't collect or maintain any personal information except your IP. Your IP is used to determine your location and thereby assist us in displaying relevant search results and advertisements.

3\. More Information.
---------------------

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit http://www.netcoalition.com and http://www.privacyalliance.org. If you wish to be notified of any updates to this Privacy Policy, please check back frequently as any updates will be posted to Oscobo.com with a new effective date.

4\. Contacting Oscobo
---------------------

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy and your rights under this policy, please write to us at the address below.

Becovi Media Limited  
5TH Floor, Nova Atria North, Blackthorn Road, Sandyford Business Park, Sandyford, Dublin D18F5X2, Ireland

© 2024 - oscobo.com    [Download Oscobo Browser](https://www.oscobo.com/ctnt.php?c=download&a=&u=&t=) | [Terms of Service](https://www.oscobo.com/ctnt.php?c=terms&a=&u=&t=) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.oscobo.com/ctnt.php?c=privacy&a=&u=&t=) | [About](https://www.oscobo.com/ctnt.php?c=aboutus&a=&u=&t=) | [Press](https://www.oscobo.com/ctnt.php?c=press&a=&u=&t=) | [Contact](https://www.oscobo.com/ctnt.php?c=contactus&a=&u=&t=)
